(gentle upbeat music)
♪ I don't need no bible ♪
♪ Just look in my eyes ♪
♪ I've waited so long, baby ♪
♪ Now that we're friends ♪
♪ Every man's got his patience ♪
♪ And here's where mine ends ♪
♪ I want your ♪
(gentle upbeat music ends)
(suspenseful organ music)
(spirited upbeat music)
♪ Well, I guess it would be nice
if I could touch your body ♪
♪ I know not everybody
has got a body like you ♪
♪ But I gotta think twice
before I give my heart away ♪
♪ And I know all the games you play ♪
♪ Because I play them, too ♪
♪ Oh, but I need some time
off from that emotion ♪
♪ Time to pick my heart up off the floor ♪
♪ Oh, when that love comes
down without devotion ♪
♪ Well, it takes a strong man, baby ♪
♪ But I'm showin' you the door ♪
♪ 'Cause I gotta have faith ♪
♪ I gotta have faith ♪
♪ Because I gotta have faith, faith ♪
♪ I got to have faith, faith, faith ♪
♪ Baby, I know you're askin' me to stay ♪
♪ Say "Please, please,
please don't go away" ♪
♪ You say I'm givin' you the blues ♪
♪ Maybe you mean every word you say ♪
♪ Can't help but think of yesterday ♪
♪ And another who tied me
down to lover boy rules ♪
♪ Before this river becomes an ocean ♪
♪ Before you throw my
heart back on the floor ♪
♪ Oh, baby, I reconsider
my foolish notion ♪
♪ Well, I need someone to hold me ♪
♪ But I'll wait for somethin' more ♪
♪ Yes, I gotta have faith ♪
♪ Ooh, I gotta have faith ♪
♪ Because I gotta have
faith, faith, faith ♪
♪ I gotta have faith, faith, faith, uh ♪
(spirited upbeat music continues)
(George vocalizing)
♪ I'll just have to wait ♪
♪ Because I've got to have faith ♪
♪ I gotta have faith ♪
♪ I've got to, got to, got to have faith ♪
♪ Before this river becomes an ocean ♪
♪ Before you throw my
heart back on the floor ♪
♪ I just gotta have faith ♪
♪ Oh, oh, baby ♪
♪ I reconsider my foolish notion ♪
♪ Well, I need someone to hold me ♪
♪ But I'll wait for somethin' more ♪
♪ 'Cause I gotta have faith ♪
(spirited upbeat music)
♪ Ooh, I gotta have faith ♪
♪ Because I gotta have
faith, faith, faith ♪
♪ I gotta have faith, faith, faith, uh ♪